<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Creative Apps</string>
    <string name="hw1_name">LeeTorvalds</string>
    <string name="hw1_app_name">Guess the number</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello" \n 2&gt;3 3&lt;2 &amp;world!</string>
    <string name="lilliac_1">Lilliac 1</string>
    <string name="caption">        The ILLIAC I (Illinois Automatic Computer), a pioneering computer built in 1952 by the University of Illinois, was the 
        first computer built and owned entirely by a US educational institution. ILLIAC I was based on the IAS Von Neumann 
        architecture as described by mathematician John von Neumann in his influential First Draft of a Report on the EDVAC. 
        Unlike most computers of its era, the ILLIAC I and ORDVAC computers were twin copies of the same design, with software 
        compatibility. The computer had 2,800 vacuum tubes, measured 10 ft (3 m) by 2 ft (0.6 m) by 8½ ft (2.6 m) (L×B×H), and 
        weighed 5 tons (4.5 t). ILLIAC I was very powerful for its time; in 1956 it had more computing power than all of Bell Labs.
        Because the lifetime of the tubes within ILLIAC was about a year, the machine was shut down every day 
        for "preventive maintenance" when older vacuum tubes would be replaced in order to increase reliability. 
        Visiting scholars from Japan assisted in the design of the ILLIAC series of computers, and later developed the 
        MUSASINO-1 computer in Japan. ILLIAC I was retired in 1962, when the ILLIAC II became operational.</string>
    <string name="cs_name_1">Sir Tim Berners Lee</string>
    <string name="cs_desc_1">	    Educated at Queens College, Oxford, Sir Tim Berners Lee moved into the field of computer science almost immediately 
	    upon receiving his physics degree and is widely known as the inventor of the World Wide Web. 
	    In 1989 Lee implemented the first successful communication between an HTTP client and server via what would become HTML. 
	    Lee helped invent and implement the language of the WWW, and his continued contributions have been significant as 
	    he continues to provide important input today on the still-growing infrastructure.</string>
    <string name="cs_name_2">Linus Torvalds</string>
    <string name="cs_desc_2">	    This Finnish/American engineer graduated from the University of Helsinki, and then invented a Unix operating system 
	    flavor which became Linux, one of the most widely used operating systems in the world. Linux hasn’t seen much growth 
	    in the consumer market, but has been a mainstay for programmers for decades. Most of the internet runs on Linux servers, 
	    the trademark of which is incredible stability, and strong security. Torvalds continues his work, sponsored by the Linux 
	    foundation, and his continued contributions to the Linux platform have continued to change computing for everybody, 
	    albeit behind the scenes.</string>
    <string name="image_description">famous computer scientist image</string>
    <string name="hw1_question">Guess the number between 1 and 20. You can try 5 times</string>
    <string name="hw1_input_hint">Enter guessing number</string>
    <string name="hw1_result">You have 5 Attempts</string>
    <string name="peer1_ee">Introduction to Electrical Engineering</string>
    <string name="lyrics">Don’t call me darlin’\nDon’t call me babe\nCuz I’m not your darlin’\nAnd I never will be\n
	    All your sweet nothings\nMean nothing to me\nSo don’t call me darlin’\nIt ain’t that easy\n\n
	    You saw something you wanted\nMade a strategy\nBut your eyes wander all over\nIt’s no mystery\n
	    But baby older don’t mean wiser\nAnd your smile don’t make you’re kind,\n
	    Oh your disguise don’t mean you’re hiding a thing, oh\n\nDon’t call me darlin, I won’t be coming around tonight\n
	    I know your kindness comes with second intentions\nSome cannot see through you&#8212; let me do you a solid\n
	    And point you the other way\nBaby, don’t call me darlin today\n\nYou think you’ll hit your target\n
	    If you keep on firing\nSo sure that I’m gonna soften up\nTo you over time\n\nBut baby stronger don’t mean smarter\n
	    When you push you push me farther,\nAll that flattery won’t get you to me, oh  </string>
    <string name="coverartDescription">softfocus piano (covert art)</string>
    <string name="buy">Full version&#8230;</string>
    <string name="facebook">FaceBook</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nasa">0g</string>
	<string name="title_activity_surprise">Surprise</string>
</resources>
